capfriendly.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - CapFriendly - NHL Salary Caps

Date of Most Recent Revision: May 24, 2018

### INTRODUCTION

CapFriendly Inc. ("CapFriendly") (the "Company") provides a platform, including a website available at www.capfriendly.com, which makes available various services, including hockey related tools and content (the "Product" or “Service”). “CapFriendly,” or “we” or “us” refers to CapFriendly Inc. in this Privacy Policy. This privacy policy describes what information we collect in the use of our Products and Services, how we use that information, and what options we offer you to control your personal information.

In order to offer the Products and Services, we need to process your personal information. By using our Product you confirm that you have read and understand our Terms of Use and this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"), this includes how and why we use your personal information.

By continuing to use our Service, you acknowledge that CapFriendly will use your information in Canada and the United States, and any other locations in which it operates. If there are any questions on the content provided in this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to Contact Us.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

##### Automatically Collected Information

When you visit this Service, CapFriendly receives and records information from your browser or mobile device, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, unique device identifier, web browser, and operating system. This information along with cookies allow us to operate the Services and Product we provide to you. This information is stored in secure logs and is collected automatically. This information is used to understand how our Products and Services are used. This in turn allows us to optimize the website from a design perspective and to monetize the website through advertisements. When our Services are used, this information is collected automatically for both members that are logged in, and non-members. For members that are logged in, the collected information can include your unique CapFriendly account identifier. You account identifier is used to identify how our Products and Services are used by active members as opposed to non-members using the site. We do not share the information that is collected automatically by the servers that run our Service with any third-parties.

##### Information You Provide To Us

 **Account Registration**

CapFriendly allows for anonymous pseudonym participation and no personal information is required with the exception of an email address and birthday. We require an email address to verify that you are a human being (to prevent spam from an automated bot for example). Your email address is used to send you a unique code upon registration; to send you a unique code if you need to edit your password; and as a verification method if you need to contact us because you have forgotten your account name, password, or want to deactivate your account. We do not use your email for promotional emails and do not share your email with any third parties.

We require users to be 13 years of age or older to use our Services as explained in the Terms of Use, and for this reason we require your date of birth when registering to CapFriendly. We do not share your birthday with any third parties. You can opt-in to display your birthday in the forums, in which case your date of birth would be made public.

Your username (which can be a pseudonym or other anyonymous name) will be displayed publicly on your profile, in the forums, and on tools in which you publish (such as Armchair-GM or Mock-Draft, for example).

 **Profile Information**

By registering and creating a profile for our Services, optional profile fields that are completed will be displayed publicly. These optional fields include an uploaded avatar or profile picture, location, biography, user title and favourite hockey teams. These optional fields are not required to use the Services offered by CapFriendly; however, if you opt to include them, the information will be displayed publicly.

 **Forums**

The CapFriendly forums are a publicly visible message board. Any and all information you include in a forum post or forum thread will be displayed publicly. All information submitted will be displayed to members and non-members. You should be aware that any personal information (for example: name, age, location, birthplace, street address, email address, or telephone number) that you include on a forum post or forum thread can be read, collected, and used by third parties that are unrelated to CapFriendly.

### COOKIES

Cookies are used on CapFriendly in order to provide the available Services. Cookies allow us to keep track of your session (if you leave the website it allows the website to identify you when you return), keep you logged in to the website for an extended period of time, save your language preferences, and save your time-zone preferences, and other features. Generally default internet browser settings accept cookies; however, settings can be changed to refuse cookies. If you choose to disable your cookies, certain features of our Service may not function properly or at all. For example, when you login, the "Keep me logged in" feature cannot function without cookies.

Third party advertisement platforms are used on CapFriendly for monetization purposes. The advertisement companies that provide these advertisement platforms utilize cookies to deliver advertisements. If you would like more information on how these advertisement companies operate, please visit the non-profit organization [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### PRIVACY POLICY ACCEPTANCE

By continuing to use the Service or Product provided by CapFriendly, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy

### ACCOUNT DEACTIVATION OR DELETION

If you would like to have your CapFriendly account and the respective data deleted or deactivated, please email us at [contact@capfriendly.com](mailto:contact@capfriendly.com) and we would be happy to do so.

### CONTACT US

If you would like to get in contact with the CapFriendly webmasters, please use one of the methods specified on the Contact Us page.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We reserve the right to alter or change the Privacy Policy at any time, and we encourage you to regularly check for updates on the Privacy Policy page.
